pulldownit.com 2019-03-02

# Pulldownit : Next Step in Dynamics for VFX

**THINKINETIC - PRIVACY POLICY**

We are committed to protect the privacy of your personal data submitted to us through the web site. This document contains information regarding  our privacy protection  policy.

**Data Controller**

THINKINETIC  is the “data controller” of all personal information that is collected and used about  our customers and visitors for the purposes of EU-wide GPDR. THINKINETIC  is owned  by Carlos Pegar,  registered in Spain, with VAT number ES02535891A  and registered office at Campezo 14 portal 3 app 4-15 Madrid 28022, Spain.

**What personal data we collect**

When you buy our software or engage in activities on our website, such as subscribe to our newsletter or contact technical support, we may ask you to provide us with a limited amount of personal information. The information is necessary for us to process your purchase or provide requested service. BY CHOOSING TO ENTER OR SUBMIT THE REQUESTED INFORMATION, YOU AGREE WITH THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

**What do we use your personal data for**

We collect and store information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other manner to process your purchase, respond to your requests for services, improve our website, products and services, as well as communicate with you on promotional offers, bonuses, sales, and related marketing information and actions. We do not sell, rent, lease or disclose customer information to third parties.

**how long will we keep your data for**

We will aim to retain your personal data only as long as necessary for the purposes of the processing which are explained above, and any secondary purposes such as audit, regulatory and legal record-keeping requirements.

**Sharing of your personal data**

Your personal data may be shared  with other companies being partners of  THINKINETIC. 

We are committed to protecting customer privacy and personal information you  provide to us. THINKINETIC WILL NOT SELL OR DISCLOSE CUSTOMER INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES UNLESS REQUIRED BY LAW, LEGAL PROCESS OR IN THE GOOD FAITH BELIEF THAT SUCH ACTION IS NECESSARY TO PROTECT THE RIGHTS OR PROPERTY OF THINKINETIC OR PROTECT THE SAFETY OF THINKINETIC USERS.

**Security**

Your personal information is transmitted via SSL (a network protocol for the secure transmission of data) in encrypted form. Our web site is protected against disclosure, destruction or unauthorized access. However no data transmission over the internet is 100% secure, we cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

**Your data protection rights**

You have the right to **request information** about whether we hold personal information about you, and, if so, what that information is and **request access** to your personal information to receive a copy of it to check that we are lawfully processing it.

Likewise you have the right to **request correction** of the personal information that we hold about you when it is any incomplete or  inaccurate . You have the right **request erasure** of your personal information where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it.

Complementary, under certain circumstances,  you have the right to,

**Object to processing** of your personal information where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) or **Request the restriction of processing** of your personal information.

**Withdraw consent.**

In the limited circumstances where you may have provided your consent to the collection, processing and transfer of your personal information for a specific purpose, you have the right to withdraw your consent for that specific processing at any time. Once we have received notification that you have withdrawn your consent, we will no longer process your information for the purpose or purposes you originally agreed to, unless we have another legitimate basis for doing so in law.

**Submit your request**

The User is informed that at any time he / she can exercise the mentioned rights by writing to us in the following email: [gdpr@pulldownit.com](mailto:gdpr@pulldownit.com), attaching a copy of your ID card.

You have the right to make a complaint at any time to a supervisory authority. The “Agencia Española de Protección de Datos” (Spanish Data Protection Agency) is the lead data protection supervisory authority for THINKINETIC as a Spanish data controller. You can find more information at [https://www.agpd.es/](https://www.agpd.es/)
